American Federation of Labor Records, Part 2 on Microfilm 5760 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Relations with the Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1935-1950 (Reel 19)
  - 0387. Box 24/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 12 pages., 1942; 7 (Reel 19)
    January-June 1942.
  - 0399. Box 25/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1942-1943; 8 (Reel 19)
  - 0400. Box 25/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 80 pages., 1942; 9 (Reel 19)
    April and August- December, 1942.
  - 0480. Box 25/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 64 pages., 1943; 10 (Reel 19)
    January-June 1943.
  - 0544. Box 25/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1943-1944; 11 (Reel 19)
  - 0545. Box 25/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 84 pages., 1943; 12 (Reel 19)
    January- November 1943.
  - 0629. Box 25/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 26 pages., 1944; 13 (Reel 19)
    January- November 1944.
  - 0655. Box 25/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1945-1947; 14 (Reel 19)
  - 0656. Box 25/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 15 pages., 1945; 15 (Reel 19)
    October- December 1945.
  - 0671. Box 25/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 93 pages., 1946; 16 (Reel 19)
    January- December 1946.
  - 0764. Box 25/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 58 pages., 1947; 17 (Reel 19)
    January-July 1947
- Relations with the Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1935-1950 Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1937-1947. (Reel 20)
  - 0001. Box 25/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1948-1950; 1 (Reel 20)
  - 0002. Box 25/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 40 pages., 1948; 2 (Reel 20)
    September- December 1948
  - 0042. Box 25/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 26 pages., 1949; 3 (Reel 20)
    January-October 1949.
  - 0068. Box 25/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 47 pages., 1950; 4 (Reel 20)
    May-September 1950.
  - 0116. Box 26/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1937-1938; 5 (Reel 20)
  - 0117. Box 26/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 125 pages., 1937; 6 (Reel 20)
    May-December 1937.
  - 0242. Box 26/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 141 pages., 1938; 7 (Reel 20)
    January-March 1938.
  - 0383.Box 26/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1938-1939; 8 (Reel 20)
  - 0384. Box 26/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 187 pages., 1938; 9 (Reel 20)
    April-December 1938.
  - 0571. Box 26/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 38 pages., 1939; 10 (Reel 20)
    January-March 1939.
  - 0609. Box 26/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1939-1944; 11 (Reel 20)
    1939-1940, 1943-1944
  - 0610. Box 26/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 35 pages., 1939; 12 (Reel 20)
    April-December 1939
  - 0645. Box 26/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 19 pages., 1940; 13 (Reel 20)
    January-October 1940.
  - 0664. Box 26/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 69 pages., 1943; 14 (Reel 20)
    February-December 1943.
  - 0733. Box 26/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 168 pages., 1944; 15 (Reel 20)
    January-March 1944.
- Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations Papers Favoring American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations Unity, 1935-1951. (Reel 21)
  - 0001. Box 26/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1944-1947; 1 (Reel 21)
    1944, 1947.
  - 0002. Box 26/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 119 pages., 1944; 2 (Reel 21)
    April-December 1944.
  - 0121. Box 26/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Political Collaboration with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 86 pages., 1947; 3 (Reel 21)
    January-December 1947
  - 0207. Box 27/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1935-1936; 4 (Reel 21)
  - 0208. Box 27/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 27 pages., 1935; 5 (Reel 21)
    November-December 1935.
  - 0235. Box 27/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 244 pages., 1936; 6 (Reel 21)
    January- December 1936
  - 0479. Box 27/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 191 pages., 1937; 7 (Reel 21)
    January- September 1937.
  - 0670. Box 27/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 182 pages., 1937; 8 (Reel 21)
    October 1937.
- Papers Favoring American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations Unity, 1935-1951 (Continued). (Reel 22)
  - 0001. Box 27/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 292 pages., 1937; 1 (Reel 22)
    November-December 1937
  - 0293. Box 27/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 215 pages., 1938; 2 (Reel 22)
    January- April 1938.
  - 0508. Box 28/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 120 pages., 1938; 3 (Reel 22)
    May- September 1938.
  - 0628. Box 28/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 206 pages., 1938; 4 (Reel 22)
    October 1938.
  - 0834. Box 28/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 145 pages., 1938; 5 (Reel 22)
    November-December 1938.
- Papers Favoring American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations Unity, 1935-1951 (Continued). (Reel 23)
  - 0001. Box 28/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 188 pages., 1939; 1 (Reel 23)
    January- February 1939
  - 0190. Box 28/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 218 pages., 1939; 2 (Reel 23)
    March 1-9, 1939.
  - 0408. Box 28/Folder 6. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 255 pages., 1939; 3 (Reel 23)
    March 9-14, 1939.
  - 0663. Box 29/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 272 pages., 1939; 4 (Reel 23)
    March 15-31, 1939.
- Papers Favoring American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations Unity, 1935-1951 (Continued). National and International Union Correspondence, 1935-1951. (Reel 24)
  - 0001. Box 29/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 248 pages., 1939; 1 (Reel 24)
    April- May 1939.
  - 0249. Box 29/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 149 pages., 1939; 2 (Reel 24)
    June- December 1939.
  - 0388. Box 29/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 107 pages., 1940; 3 (Reel 24)
    January- December 1940.
  - 0595. Box 29/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1941-1951; 4 (Reel 24)
  - 0596. Box 29/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 16 pages., 1941; 5 (Reel 24)
    June- December 1941.
  - 0612. Box 29/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 82 pages., 1942; 6 (Reel 24)
    January- September 1942.
  - 0694. Box 29/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 1 page., 1943; 7 (Reel 24)
    September 1943.
  - 0695. Box 29/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 2 pages., 1944; 8 (Reel 24)
    March 1944.
  - 0697. Box 29/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 3 pages., 1945; 9 (Reel 24)
    March 1945
  - 0700. Box 29/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 7 pages., 1946; 10 (Reel 24)
    December 1946
  - 0707. Box 29/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 63 pages., 1947; 11 (Reel 24)
    January- August 1947
  - 0770. Box 29/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 1 page., 1950; 12 (Reel 24)
    April 1950
  - 0771. Box 29/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers Favoring Unity with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 7 pages., 1951; 13 (Reel 24)
    April-May 1951.
  - 0778. Box 30/Folder 1. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "A", 14 (Reel 24)
  - 0779. Box 30/Folder 1. Actors. 2 pages., 1937-1938; 15 (Reel 24)
  - 0781. Box 30/Folder 1. Auto Workers. 261 pages., 1935-1938; 16 (Reel 24)
- National and International Union Correspondence, 1935-1951 (Reel 25)
  - 0001. Box 30/Folder 2. Correspondence of National and International Unions. Auto Workers (continued). 143 pages., 1939-1950; 1 (Reel 25)
  - 0144. Box 30/Folder 3. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "B", 2 (Reel 25)
  - 0145. Box 30/Folder 5. Bakers. 8 pages., 1942-1943; 3 (Reel 25)
  - 0153. Box 30/Folder 3. Barbers. 5 pages., 1936-1951; 4 (Reel 25)
    1936 and 1951.
  - 0158. Box 30/Folder 3. Blacksmiths. 79 pages., 1936-1943; 5 (Reel 25)
  - 0237. Box 30/Folder 3. Boilermakers. 14 pages., 1937-1947; 6 (Reel 25)
  - 0251. Box 30/Folder 3. Boot and Shoe Workers. 35 pages., 1936-1944; 7 (Reel 25)
  - 0286. Box 30/Folder 4. Brewery Workers. 8 pages., 1936-1942; 8 (Reel 25)
    1936 and 1942
  - 0294. Box 30/Folder 3. Brick and Clay Workers. 14 pages., 1939-1943; 9 (Reel 25)
  - 0308. Box 30/Folder 3. Bridge Workers. 31 pages., 1936-1947; 10 (Reel 25)
  - 0339. Box 30/Folder 3. Building Service Employees. 18 pages., 1937-1949; 11 (Reel 25)
  - 0357. Box 30/Folder 4. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "C", 12 (Reel 25)
  - 0358. Box 30/Folder 4. Railroad Carmen. 5 pages., 1940-1947; 13 (Reel 25)
    1940 and 1947
  - 0363. Box 30/Folder 4. Carpenters. 103 pages., 1935-1950; 14 (Reel 25)
  - 0466. Box 30/Folder 4. Cement Workers. 94 pages., 1940-1944; 15 (Reel 25)
  - 0560. Box 40/Folder 5. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "C" (continued)-"F", 16 (Reel 25)
  - 0561. Box 30/Folder 5. Cigar Makers. 13 pages., 1937-1947; 17 (Reel 25)
    1937-1939 and 1947
  - 0574.. Box 30/Folder 5. Cleaners and Dyers. 2 pages., 1947; 18 (Reel 25)
  - 0574. Box 30/Folder 5. Clerks. 41 pages., 1936-1945; 19 (Reel 25)
  - 0615. Box 30/Folder 5. Electrical Workers. 33 pages., 1936-1951; 20 (Reel 25)
  - 0648. Box 30/Folder 5. Farm Equipment Workers. 6 pages., 1943-1944; 21 (Reel 25)
  - 0654. Box 30/Folder 5. Firemen and Oilers. 3 pages., 1944; 22 (Reel 25)
  - 0657. Box 30/Folder 5. Fur Workers. 169 pages., 1937-1943; 23 (Reel 25)
  - 0826. Box 31/Folder 1. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "F" (continued)-"G", 24 (Reel 25)
  - 0827. Box 31/Folder 1. Furniture Workers. 3 pages., 1944; 25 (Reel 25)
  - 0830. Box 31/Folder 1. Garment Workers. 140 pages., 1935-1944; 26 (Reel 25)
  - 0970. Box 31/Folder 1. Glass Workers. 36 pages., 1937-1947; 27 (Reel 25)
  - 1006. Box 31/Folder 1. Glove Workers. 3 pages., 1937; 28 (Reel 25)
- National and International Union Correspondence, 1935-1951 (Reel 26)
  - 0001. Box 31/Folder 2. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "G"" (continued)-"J", 1 (Reel 26)
  - 0002. Box 31/Folder 2. Government Employees. 10 pages., 1936-1942; 2 (Reel 26)
    1936 and 1941-1942
  - 0012. Box 31/Folder 2. Grain Processors. 4 pages., 1942; 3 (Reel 26)
  - 0016. Box 31/Folder 2. Handbag Workers. 29 pages., 1938-1945; 4 (Reel 26)
    1938 and 1945
  - 0045. Box 31/Folder 2. Hatters. 41 pages., 1936-1947; 5 (Reel 26)
    1936-1939 and 1945-1947
  - 0086. Box 31/Folder 2. Hod Carriers. 7 pages., 1939-1943; 6 (Reel 26)
  - 0093. Box 31/Folder 2. Hotel and Restaurant Employees. 55 pages., 1936-1947; 7 (Reel 26)
  - 0148. Box 31/Folder 2. Jewelry Workers. 16 pages., 1938-1940; 8 (Reel 26)
  - 0164. Box 31/Folder 3. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "L"-"M", 9 (Reel 26)
  - 0165. Box 31/Folder 3. Laundry Workers. 4 pages., 1943; 10 (Reel 26)
  - 0169. Box 31/Folder 3. Leather Workers. 6 pages., 1937; 11 (Reel 26)
  - 0175. Box 31/Folder 3. Leather Carriers. 3 pages., 1944-1945; 12 (Reel 26)
  - 0178. Box 31/Folder 3. Locomotive Engineers. 2 pages., 1947; 13 (Reel 26)
  - 0180. Box 31/Folder 3. Longshoremen. 46 pages., 1937-1945; 14 (Reel 26)
  - 0226. Box 31/Folder 3. Machinists. 95 pages., 1936-1945; 15 (Reel 26)
  - 0321. Box 31/Folder 3. Maintenance of Way. 7 pages., 1936-1939; 16 (Reel 26)
    1936 and 1939
  - 0328. Box 31/Folder 3. Marine engineers. 23 pages., 1937-1945; 17 (Reel 26)
  - 0351. Box 31/Folder 3. Maritime Union. 16 pages., 1939; 18 (Reel 26)
  - 0367. Box 31/Folder 3. Metal Polishers. 9 pages., 1936-1942; 19 (Reel 26)
    1936, 1940, and 1942
  - 0376. Box 31/Folder 3. Match Workers. 3 pages., 1942; 20 (Reel 26)
  - 0379. Box 31/Folder 3. Meat Cutters. 34 pages., 1937-1950; 21 (Reel 26)
  - 0413. Box 31/Folder 4. Correspondence of National and International Unions. Mine Workers. 262 pages., 1935-1937; 22 (Reel 26)
    1935-July 1937
  - 0676. Box 31/Folder 5. Correspondence of National and International Unions. Mine Workers. 210 pages., 1937-1938; 23 (Reel 26)
    August 1937-May 1938
  - 0886. Box 32/Folder 1. Correspondence of National and International Unions. Mine Workers. 215 pages., 1938-1939; 24 (Reel 26)
    June 1938-August 1939.
- National and International Union Correspondence, 1935-1951 (Reel 27)
  - 0001. Box 32/Folder 2. Correspondence of National and International Unions. Mine Workers. 161 pages., 1939-1947; 1 (Reel 27)
    October 1939-July 1947
  - 0162. Box 32/Folder 3. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "M" (continued)-"O", 2 (Reel 27)
  - 0163. Box 32/Folder 3. Molders. 36 pages., 1937-1945; 3 (Reel 27)
    1937, 1941, and 1943-1945
  - 0199. Box 32/Folder 3. Municipal Employees. 23 pages., 1937-1951; 4 (Reel 27)
    1937-1943 and 1947-1951.
  - 0222. Box 32/Folder 3. Musicians. 22 pages., 1937-1947; 5 (Reel 27)
    1937, 1941, and 1947
  - 0244. Box 32/Folder 3. Office Workers. 34 pages., 1941-1947; 6 (Reel 27)
  - 0278. Box 32/Folder 3. Oil Field Workers. 38 pages., 1937-1944; 7 (Reel 27)
  - 0316. Box 32/Folder 3. Operating Engineers. 9 pages., 1937-1943; 8 (Reel 27)
    1937 and 1943
  - 0325. Box 32/Folder 4. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "P"-"R", 9 (Reel 27)
  - 0326. Box 32/Folder 4. Painters. 40 pages., 1938-1947; 10 (Reel 27)
  - 0366. Box 32/Folder 4. Photo Engravers. 2 pages., 1936; 11 (Reel 27)
  - 0368. Box 32/Folder 4. Plasterers. 2 pages., 1936; 12 (Reel 27)
  - 0370. Box 32/Folder 4. Polishers, Metal. 1 page., 1936; 13 (Reel 27)
  - 0371. Box 32/Folder 4. Plumbers. 3 pages., 1939; 14 (Reel 27)
  - 0374. Box 32/Folder 4. Powder Workers. 8 pages., 1939; 15 (Reel 27)
  - 0382. Box 32/Folder 4. Rubber Workers. 5 pages., 1938-1939; 16 (Reel 27)
  - 0387. Box 32/Folder 4. Printing Pressmen. 11 pages., 1936-1945; 17 (Reel 27)
    1936 and 1945
  - 0398. Box 32/Folder 4. Quarry Workers. 79 pages., 1937-1938; 18 (Reel 27)
  - 0477. Box 32/Folder 5. Correspondence of National and International Unions. Newspaper Guild. 339 pages., 1937-1945; 19 (Reel 27)
  - 0816. Box 32/Folder 6. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "P", 20 (Reel 27)
  - 0817. Box 32/Folder 6. Packinghouse Workers. 2 pages., 1947; 21 (Reel 27)
  - 0819. Box 32/Folder 6. Paper Makers. 57 pages., 1936-1947; 22 (Reel 27)
  - 0876. Box 32/Folder 6. Pattern Makers. 20 pages., 1939-1945; 23 (Reel 27)
  - 0896. Box 33/Folder 1. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "R" (continued)-"S", 24 (Reel 27)
  - 0897. Box 33/Folder 1. Railway Employees. 26 pages., 1940-1943; 25 (Reel 27)
  - 0923. Box 33/Folder 1. Rubber Workers. 9 pages., 1936-1947; 26 (Reel 27)
    1936 and 1947
  - 0932. Box 33/Folder 1. Seafarers. 65 pages., 1937-1945; 27 (Reel 27)
  - 0997. Box 33/Folder 1. Sheep Shearers. 4 pages., 1938; 28 (Reel 27)
  - 1001. Box 33/Folder 1. Shipbuilders. 4 pages., 1943-1947; 29 (Reel 27)
    1943 and 1947
  - 1005. Box 33/Folder 1. Shoe Workers. 2 pages., 1947; 30 (Reel 27)
  - 1007. Box 33/Folder 1. Sleeping Car Porters. 11 pages., 1940; 31 (Reel 27)
- National and International Union Correspondence, 1935-1951 State Federations of Labor Correspondence, 1935-1945. (Reel 28)
  - 0001. Box 33/Folder 2. Correspondence of National and International Unions. Steel Workers. 269 pages., 1933-1936; 1 (Reel 28)
    1933-March 1936
  - 0270. Box 33/Folder 3. Correspondence of National and International Unions. Steel Workers. 190 pages., 1936-1947; 2 (Reel 28)
  - 0460. Box 33/Folder 4. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "S" (continued)-"T", 3 (Reel 28)
  - 0461. Box 33/Folder 4. Switchmen. 3 pages., 1936; 4 (Reel 28)
  - 0464. Box 33/Folder 4. Teachers. 29 pages., 1937-1947; 5 (Reel 28)
  - 0493. Box 33/Folder 4. Teamsters. 50 pages., 1936-1945; 6 (Reel 28)
  - 0543. Box 33/Folder 4. Technical Engineers. 10 pages., 1937-1945; 7 (Reel 28)
  - 0553. Box 33/Folder 4. Telegraphers. 28 pages., 1937-1944; 8 (Reel 28)
  - 0581. Box 33/Folder 4. Telephone Workers. 9 pages., 1945; 9 (Reel 28)
  - 0590. Box 33/Folder 4. Textile Workers. 41 pages., 1936-1950; 10 (Reel 28)
  - 0631. Box 33/Folder 4. Tobacco Workers. 3 pages., 1947; 11 (Reel 28)
  - 0634. Box 33/Folder 4. Trainmen, Railroad. 13 pages., 1943-1947; 12 (Reel 28)
  - 0647. Box 33/Folder 5. Typographical Union. 45 pages., 1936-1947; 13 (Reel 28)
    1936 and 1944-1947
  - 0692. Box 33/Folder 5. Correspondence of National and International Unions. "U"-"W", 14 (Reel 28)
  - 0693. Box 33/Folder 5. Upholsterers. 119 pages., 1937-1942; 15 (Reel 28)
  - 0812. Box 33/Folder 5. Wallpaper Craftsmen. 10 pages., 1944; 16 (Reel 28)
  - 0822. Box 34/Folder 1. Correspondence of State Federations of Labor. "A"-"C" and Canada, 17 (Reel 28)
  - 0823. Box 34/Folder 1. Alabama. 46 pages., 1936-1938; 18 (Reel 28)
  - 0869. Box 34/Folder 1. Arizona. 28 pages., 1937-1941; 19 (Reel 28)
  - 0897. Box 34/Folder 1. Arkansas. 28 pages., 1937-1938; 20 (Reel 28)
  - 0947. Box 34/Folder 1. California. 34 pages., 1936-1943; 21 (Reel 28)
  - 0983. Box 34/Folder 1. Canada. 54 pages., 1938-1945; 22 (Reel 28)
  - 1037. Box 34/Folder 1. Colorado. 51 pages., 1937-1939; 23 (Reel 28)
  - 1088. Box 34/Folder 1. Connecticut. 12 pages., 1937-1946; 24 (Reel 28)
- State Federations of Labor Correspondence, 1935-1945 (Reel 29)
  - 0001. Box 34/Folder 2. Correspondence of State Federations of Labor. Georgia. 287 pages., 1936-1938; 1 (Reel 29)
  - 0287. Box 34/Folder 3. Correspondence of State Federations of Labor. "I", 2 (Reel 29)
  - 0288. Box 34/Folder 3. Idaho. 14 pages., 1936-1938; 3 (Reel 29)
  - 0302. Box 34/Folder 3. Illinois. 35 pages., 1936-1946; 4 (Reel 29)
  - 0337. Box 34/Folder 3. Indiana. 37 pages., 1937-1945; 5 (Reel 29)
    1937-1938 and 1945
  - 0374. Box 34/Folder 4. Correspondence of State Federations of Labor. "I" (continued)-"L", 6 (Reel 29)
  - 0375. Box 34/Folder 4. Iowa. 190 pages., 1936-1944; 7 (Reel 29)
  - 0565. Box 34/Folder 4. Kansas. 2 pages., 1936; 8 (Reel 29)
  - 0567. Box 34/Folder 4. Kentucky. 3 pages., 1936; 9 (Reel 29)
  - 0570. Box 34/Folder 4. Kansas. 5 pages., 1937-1939; 10 (Reel 29)
  - 0575. Box 34/Folder 4. Kentucky. 2 pages., 1938; 11 (Reel 29)
  - 0577. Box 34/Folder 4. Kansas. 31 pages., 1939-1941; 12 (Reel 29)
  - 0608. Box 34/Folder 4. Kentucky. 61 pages., 1937-1942; 13 (Reel 29)
  - 0669. Box 34/Folder 4. Kansas. 1 page., 1937; 14 (Reel 29)
  - 0670. Box 34/Folder 4. Louisiana. 13 pages., 1946; 15 (Reel 29)
  - 0683. Box 35/Folder 1. Correspondence of State Federations of Labor. "M", 16 (Reel 29)
  - 0684. Box 35/Folder 1. Maryland. 9 pages., 1936-1937; 17 (Reel 29)
  - 0693. Box 35/Folder 1. Massachusetts. 26 pages., 1936-1938; 18 (Reel 29)
  - 0719. Box 35/Folder 1. Michigan. 17 pages., 1937-1939; 19 (Reel 29)
  - 0736. Box 35/Folder 1. Minnesota. 77 pages., 1936-1945; 20 (Reel 29)
  - 0813. Box 35/Folder 1. Mississippi. 9 pages., 1936; 21 (Reel 29)
  - 0822. Box 35/Folder 1. Minnesota. 2 pages., 1947; 22 (Reel 29)
  - 0824. Box 35/Folder 1. Mississippi. 4 pages., 1937; 23 (Reel 29)
  - 0828. Box 35/Folder 2. Correspondence of State Federations of Labor. Montana. 233 pages., 1937-1939; 24 (Reel 29)
- State Federations of Labor Correspondence, 1935-1945 (Reel 30)
  - 0001. Box 35/Folder 3. Correspondence of State Federations of Labor. "N"-"O", 1 (Reel 30)
  - 0002. Box 35/Folder 3. Nebraska. 12 pages., 1944-1945; 2 (Reel 30)
  - 0014. Box 35/Folder 3. North Carolina. 3 pages., 1945; 3 (Reel 30)
  - 0017. Box 35/Folder 3. New York. 1 page., 1945; 4 (Reel 30)
  - 0018. Box 35/Folder 3. Nebraska. 1 page., 1945; 5 (Reel 30)
  - 0019. Box 35/Folder 3. Nevada. 25 pages., 1937-1938; 6 (Reel 30)
  - 0044. Box 35/Folder 3. New Hampshire. 5 pages., 1937; 7 (Reel 30)
  - 0049. Box 35/Folder 3. New Jersey. 24 pages., 1936-1951; 8 (Reel 30)
    1936-1937, 1943, and 1951.
  - 0073. Box 35/Folder 3. New Mexico. 3 pages., 1937; 9 (Reel 30)
  - 0076. Box 35/Folder 3. New York. 4 pages., 1937; 10 (Reel 30)
  - 0080. Box 35/Folder 3. North Carolina. 66 pages., 1936-1939; 11 (Reel 30)
  - 0146. Box 35/Folder 3. North Dakota. 12 pages., 1936-1937; 12 (Reel 30)
  - 0158. Box 35/Folder 3. Ohio. 49 pages., 1936-1938; 13 (Reel 30)
  - 0207. Box 35/Folder 3. Oklahoma. 37 pages., 1935-1950; 14 (Reel 30)
    1935-1937 and 1950
  - 0244. Box 35/Folder 4. Correspondence of State Federations of Labor. Pennsylvania. 287 pages., 1936-1947; 15 (Reel 30)
  - 0532. Box 36/Folder 1. Correspondence of State Federations of Labor. "R"-W", 16 (Reel 30)
  - 0533. Box 36/Folder 1. Rhode Island. 10 pages., 1937-1938; 17 (Reel 30)
  - 0543. Box 36/Folder 1. South Carolina. 10 pages., 1936-1937; 18 (Reel 30)
  - 0553. Box 36/Folder 1. South Dakota. 16 pages., 1937; 19 (Reel 30)
  - 0569. Box 36/Folder 1. Tennessee. 14 pages., 1936-1937; 20 (Reel 30)